<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; techamica</title>
	<atom:link href="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 11:31:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Art of Cooking</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 11:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is our favorite recipe for poblano and onion hash browns. This is a dish you can easily improvise with and add your own flare to make it your own. Everyone we’ve made this for absolutely loves it! What You’ll &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is our favorite recipe for poblano and onion hash browns. This is a dish you can easily improvise with and add your own flare to make it your own. Everyone we’ve made this for absolutely loves it!</p>
<p><strong>What You’ll Need</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>2 medium baking potatoes, peeled and shredded</li>
<li>1/2 medium onion, diced</li>
<li>1 poblano pepper, diced</li>
<li>2 Tbsp. oil</li>
<li>1 Tbsp. chili powder, or to taste</li>
<li>Salt and pepper, to taste</li>
</ul>

<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/vegetables-791892_1280-2/'><img decoding="async" width="150" height="100" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/vegetables-791892_1280-1.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/image/'><img decoding="async" width="100" height="150" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/image.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/random-picture/'><img decoding="async" width="150" height="99" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/Random-Picture.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/greens-266560_1280/'><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="99" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/greens-266560_1280.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p><strong>Preparation and Cooking</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Soak the shredded potatoes in cold water for about 30 minutes. Drain and pat dry with paper towels, removing as much moisture as possible.</li>
<li>In a large bowl, combine the shredded potatoes, onion, and poblano pepper and stir.</li>
<li>Place a large, heavy skillet over medium-high heat and add the oil. Once hot, add the potato mixture, sprinkle with half the chili powder and cook until the bottom begins to brown (about 5 to 7 minutes).</li>
<li>Flip over, or stir, the hash browns. Add the remaining chili powder and cook for an additional 5 to 7 minutes. Once desired crispiness is achieved, season with salt and pepper, if desired, and serve.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/art-of-cooking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On the hunt for Adventure</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/on-the-hunt-for-adventure/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/on-the-hunt-for-adventure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 09:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Pacific Northwest, sometimes referred to as Cascadia, is a region in western North America bounded by the Pacific Ocean to the west and, loosely, by the Rocky Mountains on the east. Though no agreed boundary exists, a common conception &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Pacific Northwest, sometimes referred to as Cascadia, is a region in western North America bounded by the Pacific Ocean to the west and, loosely, by the Rocky Mountains on the east. Though no agreed boundary exists, a common conception includes the U.S. states of Oregon and Washington and the Canadian province of British Columbia. Broader conceptions reach north into Alaska and Yukon, south into far Northern California and east into Idaho and Western Montana, western Wyoming, and western Alberta, to the Continental Divide. Narrower conceptions may be limited to the Northwestern U.S. or to the coastal areas west of the Cascade and Coast mountains. The variety of definitions can be attributed to partially overlapping commonalities of the region’s history, geography, society, and other factors.</p>
<p>The Northwest Coast is the coastal regions of the Pacific Northwest and the Northwest Plateau (also commonly known as “The Interior” in British Columbia and the Inland Empire in the United States) is the inland regions. The term “Pacific Northwest” should not be confused with the Northwest Territory (also known as the Great Northwest, a historical term in the United States) or the Northwest Territories of Canada.</p>

<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/early-morning-299735_1280.jpg'><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="113" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/early-morning-299735_1280.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/forest.jpg'><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="100" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/forest.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>
<a href='https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sample.jpg'><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="100" height="150" src="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/wp-content/uploads/2016/03/sample.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail" alt="" /></a>

<p>The region’s largest metropolitan areas are Greater Seattle, Washington, with 3.7 million people; Greater Vancouver, British Columbia, with 2.4 million people; and Greater Portland, Oregon, with 2.3 million people.</p>
<p>A key aspect of the Pacific Northwest is the US–Canada international border, which the United States and the United Kingdom established at a time when the region’s inhabitants were composed mostly of Indigenous peoples. The border  in two sections, along the 49th parallel south of British Columbia and the Alaska Panhandle west of northern British Columbia  has had a powerful effect on the region. According to Canadian historian Ken Coates, the border has not merely influenced the Pacific Northwest rather, “the region’s history and character have been determined by the boundary”.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Climb the mountains and get their good tidings. Nature’s peace will flow into you as sunshine flows into trees. The winds will blow their own freshness into you, and the storms their energy, while cares will drop off like autumn leaves</strong>. <small>— John Muir</small></p></blockquote>
<p>Definitions of the Pacific Northwest region vary and there is no commonly agreed upon boundary, even among Pacific Northwesterners. A common conception of the Pacific Northwest includes the U.S. states of Oregon and Washington as well as the Canadian province of British Columbia. This definition is often restricted further to include only the coastal areas west of the crest of the Cascade Mountains and Canadian Coast Mountains. A key aspect of the Pacific Northwest is the US- Canada international border, which the United States and United Kingdom established at a time when the region’s inhabitants were composed mostly of Indigenous peoples. The border in two sections, along the 49th parallel south of British Columbia and the Alaska Panhandle west of northern British Columbia  has had a powerful effect on the region. <span style="line-height: 1.75;">According to Canadian historian Ken Coates, the border has not merely influenced the Pacific.</span></p>
<p>Definitions of the Pacific Northwest region vary and there is no commonly agreed upon boundary, even among Pacific Northwesterners. A common conception of the Pacific Northwest includes the U.S. states of Oregon and Washington as well as the Canadian province of British Columbia.</p>
<p><span style="line-height: 1.75;"> </span></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/on-the-hunt-for-adventure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
