<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; techamica</title>
	<atom:link href="https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 20:49:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2024/01/21/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2024/01/21/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 20:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2024/01/21/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keeping it Simple</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/keeping-it-simple/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/keeping-it-simple/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 06:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=99</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Over the past few months, the concepts of stripping back the superfluous, simplifying and pulling apart the true meaning of integrity have been strong personal themes. For many people, there’s a drive to again inspect old patterns that continue to &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the past few months, the concepts of stripping back the superfluous, simplifying and pulling apart the true meaning of integrity have been strong personal themes. For many people, there’s a drive to again inspect old patterns that continue to run happily in the background despite years of self-examination. Perhaps under the direction of a new global energy, there’s a sense of being able to lovingly let go of those things that have served us all well on one level, yet have offered excuses to stay small on another.</p>
<p>I came across Don Miguel Ruiz’ “The Four Agreements” the other day and it strongly resonated with this desire to pare back; to simplify; to become more real as a participant in this world and begin operating in a more authentic way.</p>
<p>With these 4 simple tenets, we could literally change the way we as humans operate in this world. How do they resonate with you? Please feel free to share your thoughts, we’d love to hear from you. If you are looking for drones, you must check out Drone Picks.</p>
<p>1. Be Impeccable with your Word: Speak with integrity. Say only what you mean. Avoid using the Word to speak against yourself or to gossip about others. Use the power of your Word in the direction of truth and love.</p>
<p>2. Don’t Take Anything Personally: Nothing others do is because of you. What others say and do is a projection of their own reality, their own dream. When you are immune to the opinions and actions of others, you won’t be the victim of needless suffering.</p>
<p>3. Don’t Make Assumptions: Find the courage to ask questions and to express what you really want. Communicate with others as clearly as you can to avoid misunderstandings, sadness and drama. With just this one agreement, you can completely transform your life.</p>
<p>4. Always Do Your Best: Your best is going to change from moment to moment; it will be different when you are healthy as opposed to sick. Under any circumstance, simply do your best, and you will avoid self-judgment, self-abuse, and regret. ~ Don Miguel Ruiz</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/keeping-it-simple/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Tall Buildings</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/making-tall-buildings/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/making-tall-buildings/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 06:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=91</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The way they are constructed, makes double hung windows very popular. Cleaning double hung windows are easier than windows based on a spiral or string system because they won&#8217;t allow the sash to drop out when you are cleaning them. &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The way they are constructed, makes double hung windows very popular. Cleaning double hung windows are easier than windows based on a spiral or string system because they won&#8217;t allow the sash to drop out when you are cleaning them. Double hung windows tilt in a way that uses a flush fitting tilt release which is more attractive than screwed in tilt release systems that are more commonly used. You may find that choosing a quality window is difficult because of the overwhelming number of options. A solid warranty offered by a quality manufacturer as well as your budget should be important factors in the window decision you make. Windows are a large investment and if you pick wisely you can save money over the long run by improving your energy efficiency. In order to save money in the future you may be wise to spend a little more on your windows now..</p>
<p>Quality doors add to the curb appeal of a home and also enhance your home&#8217;s security. Block the noise outside from entering your home with a well built door which will provide a sound barrier. Energy efficiency is the most important door feature to have. Well built doors provide tight, long-lasting barriers by using effective weather seals to improve energy efficiency. The function of door (patio, garage, front or interior door) will certainly be a factor in your decision. When you install a door ensure it is up to code and meets the safety features in your area. There are a number of design options you can choose from when it comes to doors, such as whether you would like to use coloured, textured or wrought iron glass. There are many types of materials that hand formed bevels come in like black chrome, lead, brass, copper, zinc and antique black. Breaking a door by force in order to enter your home is more difficult when you have well built security plates in your door.</p>
<p>When installing doors and windows in your house don&#8217;t forget to factor in window coverings into the price. New technology has improved the quality of shutters and blinds now available. The decision of using a shutter or blind will come down to personal preference because there are so many benefits to both. Blinds are sometimes preferred because of the flexibility they offer for installation and the variety of colours and types you can choose from. Common types of blinds include roman, roller, sheers, pleated shades or cellular shades. The fact that shutters offer home owners privacy, durability and versatility are key benefits. Shutters are designed to allow you to control the amount of privacy and light in your home. The features of light and privacy control offered by shutters makes them a popular choice. Shutters don&#8217;t shrink, fade, peel or crack, which makes them a great investment for home owners. Shutters can be cleaned easily, making them a popular choice. The ability to easily remove shutters that have a hinge-release panel makes cleaning them very accessible. Whether you want to install shutters inside the window frame or not is up to you. If you find a reliable manufacturer they will usually offer a solid warranty, perhaps even up to 25 years. The quality, type or size of window coverings you choose will impact the price.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/making-tall-buildings/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Planning</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/benefits-of-planning/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 06:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=90</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s normal to hear time management discussed in business circles; yet, it is a topic that can be of great benefit to everybody. Time is a challenge for all of us, whether we&#8217;re business people, workers, students or stay at &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s normal to hear time management discussed in business circles; yet, it is a topic that can be of great benefit to everybody. Time is a challenge for all of us, whether we&#8217;re business people, workers, students or stay at home moms or dads. There seems to be less time in today&#8217;s world, and that&#8217;s why it&#8217;s a lot more important to learn how to properly manage our time. In this article, we are going to be discussing a few key reasons why time management is so important.</p>
<p>A big benefit of time management is just how that it boosts your productivity. It is something that almost everybody hopes to be able to do. Seldom do you hear of individuals who feel that they&#8217;ve got adequate time to do the things they need and wish to do. In lots of instances, the problem is not not enough time but rather the fact that you do not have an efficient way of managing your time. Time management shows you how to set priorities, and to focus on how much time you&#8217;re wasting every day. The idea is not really to put yourself under more pressure to try and do more, but to utilize your time more wisely so you appear to have more of it.</p>
<p>One positive advantage of time management is decreased levels of stress. Not having enough time is one of the main reasons we experience stress. Think about how tense you feel if you are worrying about being late for a scheduled visit or if you&#8217;re stuck in traffic. These issues relate to time, and if you have this type of situation often you could probably benefit from some training in time management. Learning how to control schedule so that overwhelmed us and become an issue indicates that you are supervising your time efficiently. We often believe that the solution to our problems is doing things faster, but it could be even better and more relaxing if we learn how to manage our time better.</p>
<p>Time management doesn&#8217;t just includes boosting your productivity and efficiency; you also want to feel more pleasure and a better quality of life. Time is an important component of life and so we feel better about our lives when we have the ability to control our time. Conversely, feeling that we&#8217;re running out of time can create an overall feeling that we aren&#8217;t good in some part of life. Those who are genuinely successful are aware that time management is a crucial skill they have to get good at. It could be the one determining factor that lets you live in the moment and appreciate your life instead of feeling that time is a merciless boss.</p>
<p>Time management is very significant in our present times, even more so than in previous decades. Existing technology allows us to do things faster than before and yet we feel forced to continually increase the pace. As an example, we continue to have difficulty keeping track of the large number of available information even with computers and other gadgets that are extremely powerful. Time management is the component that can give us a sense of control over time so we can quit rushing and loosen up.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding Oneself in Art Gallery</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/finding-oneself-in-art-gallery/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/finding-oneself-in-art-gallery/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 06:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=85</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Decorating can be one of the most exciting times during your experience as a homeowner. Not only are you creating the essence of your home, you are also adding your very own personal touch and style. One of the easiest &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decorating can be one of the most exciting times during your experience as a homeowner. Not only are you creating the essence of your home, you are also adding your very own personal touch and style.</p>
<p>One of the easiest ways to add unique spice to an ordinarily drab room—incorporate exceptional artwork .“Many of my clients are simply amazed at how effective a colorful painting can be at bringing new life to a room that has become tired,” says Matthew Johnston, an artist known for his vibrant Tall Tulips paintings.</p>
<p>An art museum or art gallery is a building or space for the exhibition of art, usually visual art. Museums can be public or private, but what distinguishes a museum is the ownership of a collection. Paintings are the most commonly displayed art objects; however, sculpture, decorative arts, furniture, textiles, costume, drawings, pastels, watercolors, collages, prints, artists&#8217; books, photographs, and installation art are also regularly shown. Although primarily concerned with providing a space to show works of visual art, art galleries are sometimes used to host other artistic activities, such as performance art, music concerts, or poetry readings.</p>
<p>The term is used for both public galleries, which are non-profit or publicly owned museums that display selected collections of art. On the other hand, private galleries refers to the commercial enterprises for the sale of art. However, both types of gallery may host traveling exhibits or temporary exhibitions including art borrowed from elsewhere.<br />
In broad terms, in North American usage the word gallery alone often implies a private gallery, while a public gallery is more likely to be described as an art museum. In British and Commonwealth usage, the word gallery alone implies a public gallery, while a private or commercial gallery will be distinguished using those terms, and the word museum alone is generally understood to refer to institutions holding collections of historic, archaeological or scientific artefacts, rather than of fine art.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/finding-oneself-in-art-gallery/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Working Efficiently</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/working-efficiently/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/working-efficiently/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 05:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If human beings are perceived as potentials rather than problems, as possessing strengths instead of weaknesses, as unlimited rather than dull and unresponsive, then they thrive and grow to their capabilities. Information technology has entered almost in all sphere of &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If human beings are perceived as potentials rather than problems, as possessing strengths instead of weaknesses, as unlimited rather than dull and unresponsive, then they thrive and grow to their capabilities.</p>
<p>Information technology has entered almost in all sphere of our life. From electricity bill payment to shopping all are related and effected by IT in some way to other. Industries are automating their task to cut down manual labor cost. Home appliances, industrial machines, watch, automobiles are using software to enhance the quality of products. As a result demand of IT professionals is high in market.</p>
<p>IT jobs are promising, it offers hefty salary package with immense opportunity to grow and expand your career. If you are expert in your field and have good knowledge on your subject then you can easily get handsome salary package. All you need to have to build your career in It industry is right degree and skill, it is the only qualification you need to make your career in IT industry. If your are fresher and looking for primary level IT jobs then internet could help you in finding your avenue but for specialist level and higher standard IT jobs you have to rely on your professional contact as most of the organizations did not disclose higher level job opening at job portals.</p>
<p>You can start your IT career as a software engineer, web developer, database manager and IT Hardware professional. To accelerate your IT career it is important to update your skill from time to time. Learn industry level skill and enhance your capability. Course offered by SAP and Oracle are very promising though it is not easy to clear these exams but once you become SAP or Oracle certified professional you value will increase in the industry.</p>
<p>Searching IT Jobs is not a tough job there are various online portals and IT recruitment companies dealing in IT jobs. Job portals are more useful as there you can see different openings posted by numbers of IT companies. IT jobs are promising; it is one of the well-paid industries with fast growth rate. Start hunting for your dream IT job with online portals and give right shape to your career.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2016/03/14/working-efficiently/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everest Base Camp Trek</title>
		<link>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2015/05/01/everest-base-camp-trek/</link>
					<comments>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2015/05/01/everest-base-camp-trek/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[raju]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 10:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://raratheme.com/preview/business-one-page/?p=265</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Everest is the highest mountain in the world. It is not everyone’s cup of tea to assent it. However, trekking to its base camp is possible and the task is becoming increasingly easier with increase in its popularity and, therefore, &#8230; ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everest is the highest mountain in the world. It is not everyone’s cup of tea to assent it. However, trekking to its base camp is possible and the task is becoming increasingly easier with increase in its popularity and, therefore, facilities.</p>
<p>It is most definitely not a walk in the park, but if you possess a sense of adventure, will and a normally healthy body, you too can be a part of this legend. You too can enjoy the beautiful landscapes, nature and interesting culture of the Everest region.</p>
<p>Here is a guide to how you could go about making this dream a reality and, if you would want to.</p>
<p>Everest region was only moderately affected by the devastating Earthquake that hit Nepal on 25<sup>th</sup> April and 12<sup>th</sup> May.</p>
<p>Some minor landslides had crossed the trail to EBC but the villagers were quick in clearing it. After all, the trek route is firstly the means of transport for the inhabitants of the region.</p>
<p>Also, according to the team of experts sent by Tourism Agency Association of Nepal (TAAN) and engineers from Miyamoto international, all the suspension bridges to EBC are intact and safe to traverse.</p>
<p>It was mostly the teahouses that were affected. All three teahouses in Tengboche collapsed. Many of them in Phakding, Monjo, Jorsale and Pheriche were destroyed while Deboche, Dingboche and Gorakshep were unharmed. The remaining villages endured little damage.</p>
<p>Teahouse owners reported that they would be up and running by the September of 2015. September to November is the peak season for Everest Base Camp trek.</p>
<p>Indeed, EBC trek was opened and declared safe for trekking by September. The trek was possible without any added difficulty.</p>
<p>Though things have gone back to normal, there were very less trekkers this year. Locals hope that the numbers too will go back up to normal from 2016 onwards.</p>
<h3><span id="Trekking_to_Everest_Base_Camp_in_Spring">Trekking to Everest Base Camp in Spring</span></h3>
<p>Spring is one of the best seasons to trek to EBC. Clear sky and moderate temperature aside, spring offers an array of beautiful flowers. This includes Nepal’s national flower rhododendron that will make your hike uphill very pleasant.</p>
<p>Spring is also climbers’ season and one can see many colorful tents pitched on the base camp.</p>
<p>In Nepal, spring runs from March to May. However, late May may see some clouds. Mid-March is really the perfect time in terms of weather and April in terms of rhododendron and other flowers. These are also the busy times and will most probably be crowded.</p>
<h3><span id="Trekking_to_Everest_Base_Camp_in_Summer_Monsoon">Trekking to Everest Base Camp in Summer/ Monsoon</span></h3>
<p>From June to August is monsoon, though the clouds stay around till mid September.</p>
<p>Monsoon is not a good time do EBC trek. First, views will be blocked most of the time due to rain clouds. Trails will be muddy. It can rain anytime and the next village could be still an hour away. And, snow fall or snow storm at higher elevations.</p>
<p>Another problem is the delays. Flights to and from Lukla can be delayed for as long as a week. Even buses and jeeps can be delayed. In fact, they can get stuck in the soft mud en route and it is a real hassle.</p>
<p>The only good news is that leeches aren’t a problem in Everest. However, all things considered, it is better to travel to rain shadow areas like Mustang, Dolpo etc. during monsoon.</p>
<h2><span id="What_trekking_gears_or_trekking_equipment_should_I_pack">What trekking gears or trekking equipment should I pack?</span></h2>
<p>Knowing what trekking gears to pack is important. You would want to pack as light as possible while not missing the important equipments. So here is list to give you an idea.</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>A pair of trekking boots </strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Break in the shoes if needs be before hitting the trail. Trekking boots are the best though not a must.</p>
<ol start="2">
<li><strong>A pair of warm slippers</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>You can use slippers when in lodge. Warm slippers will keep you warm at higher altitude. It will be hot in lower area, especially in spring, but why carry two pair of slippers? You could carry crocs and just use woolen socks for warmth too.</p>
<ol start="3">
<li><strong>Four pair of liner socks</strong>.</li>
</ol>
<p>At least four pairs. Two warm pairs and two thin pairs. Trekking/liner socks are better but normal ones are okay too.</p>
<ol start="4">
<li><strong>Few pairs of underwear</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Few pairs of underwear, 5-7, as you see fit. Normal ones are absolutely fine but do you know you can buy ‘trekking underwear’? Not in Nepal though.</p>
<ol start="5">
<li><strong>A down jacket and a down pant </strong></li>
</ol>
<p>You could layer up but it gets really cold up there. Bringing a down jacket and pant will be much easier and you can buy or rent them in Nepal for cheap. Renting costs a dollar or less per day.</p>
<ol start="6">
<li><strong>T-shirts and trousers</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>3-4 t-shirts, mostly full sleeved for both warmth and protection from sun. 2 pair of trekking pants/trousers. Also, one to two set of clothes for your time in Kathmandu.</p>
<ol start="7">
<li><strong>A set of thermals</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>A top, bottom and underwear.</p>
<ol start="8">
<li><strong>A windproof jacket/ fleece jacket and bottoms</strong></li>
<li><strong>A light sleeping bag. </strong>You can rent or buy them in Nepal. You can also buy it outside of Nepal. If you want to buy outside of Nepal, you may want to buy one of these best backpacking sleeping bags under 100 USD.</li>
</ol>
<p>This too can be bought or rented in Nepal cheaply.</p>
<ol start="10">
<li><strong>Backpacks </strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Get yourself a nice and comfortable best hiking backpacks under $100 of 2017.</p>
<ol start="11">
<li><strong>Gety A pair of very warm Gloves</strong></li>
<li><strong>A woolen hat </strong></li>
<li><strong>Sunglasses</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Buy a pair in your home town if you don’t already own one. Fakes in Kathmandu will not be protective.</p>
<ol start="14">
<li><strong>A torchlight/ head torchlight </strong></li>
<li><strong>A First aid kit </strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Include Oral Rehydration Salts (ORS) or diarrhea tablets, blister plasters, Diamox, some pain killers and a vapor rub.</p>
<ol start="16">
<li><strong>Toiletries</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Toilet paper, hand sanitizer, water purifiers, sunscreen, moisturizer, lip balm, soap, shampoo sachets, toothpaste, toothbrush and a trekking towel.</p>
<ol start="17">
<li><strong>A water bottle</strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Not a plastic one but a metal one that can be used to fill hot water as well.</p>
<ol start="18">
<li><strong>A waterproof map of Everest Base Camp</strong></li>
<li><strong>Snacks you like and entertainment such as books, cards etc. </strong></li>
</ol>
<p>Snacks cost cheaper in Kathmandu so stock up on them in Kathmandu. Price of a snicker bar can reach up to $4 higher up in Everest.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rjghongade.github.io/techamica/2015/05/01/everest-base-camp-trek/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
